[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":509972,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":517847,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure t hat when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":15512,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":533367,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":24815,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":558189,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":4333,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":562529,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":4754,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":567287,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1583,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":568873,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the sec ond one  to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":5449,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":574326,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1756,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":576089,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4772,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":580864,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1758,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":582626,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":4294,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":586923,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<su b>6</sub > 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1864,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":588790,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":11948,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":600741,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":3983,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":604729,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <b r /><br  /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":10446,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":615182,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1769,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":616956,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your  result. )","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4564,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":621523,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1518,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":623043,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3075,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":626121,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1337,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":627461,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2820,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":630283,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1262,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":631549,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":24772,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":656329,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own  inverse  under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":48284,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":704618,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":9755,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":714382,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":5770,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":720158,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 unde r +<sub> 6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4809,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":724973,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":13268,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":738245,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":6502,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":744754,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2151,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":746909,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":3021,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":749934,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4  because  2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":39348,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":789289,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6","6"],"rt":14946,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":804241,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3880,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":808128,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible  to succ essively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":7506,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":815639,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, becau se 4 = 2  +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":107810,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":923452,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":7076,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":930540,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":2982,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":933524,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":3526,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":937053,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":1378,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":938435,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0. 10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":2915,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":941353,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1800,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":943156,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes"," No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":3309,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":946469,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1695,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":948167,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only pro duce num bers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":2151,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":950320,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":8827,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":959152,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":2081,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":961237,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":" 6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":7009,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":968254,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":10672,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":978934,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":8082,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":987023,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":3884,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":990911,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":5393,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":996307,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":15051,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1011362,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"The sum is not greater than 9.","explanation_history":["tHE","tH","t","thus ","thus","thu","th","t","The sum is not greater than 9."],"response_history":["5"],"rt":30010,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1041376,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"The sum is greater than 9. 12 subtracted by 9 is 3.","explanation_history":["The su ","The sum is greater than 9. 9 sub","The sum is greater than 9. 9 su","The sum is greater than 9. 9 s","The sum is greater than 9. 9 ","The  sum is  greater than 9. 9","The sum is greater than 9. ","The sum is greater than 9. 12 subtracted by n","The sum is greater than 9. 12 subtracted by 9 is 3."],"response_history":["3"],"rt":45977,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1087360,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"It will give back the same item.","explanation_history":["It will give back the same item."],"response_history":["0"],"rt":29769,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1117135,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":21582,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1138726,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":5803,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1144536,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9"],"rt":6669,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1151208,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"6 plus 3 equals 9","explanation_history":["6 plus 3 equals 9"],"response_history":["6"],"rt":25761,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1176973,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"Not sure but I think the answer is 0.","explanation_history":["Not t","Not sure but I think the answer is 0."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":36995,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1213977,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"Not sure. I think 0 is the generator.","explanation_history":["Yes","6 ","6","Not sure. I think 0 is the generator."],"response_history":["Yes","No"],"rt":33881,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1247867,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"5 plus 4 is 9.","explanation_history":["5 plus 4 is 9."],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":23659,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1271535,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"Yes it is less than 9","explanation_history":["Yes it is less than 9"],"response_history":["No","Yes"],"rt":27938,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1299481,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":124567,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1424053,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":21056,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1445118,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"I dont know.","explanation_history":["I dont know ","I dont know."],"response_history":["0"],"rt":29952,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1475075,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Im not sure but i think its 0.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I ","Im not sure ","Im not sure but i think its 0."],"rt":119012,"trial_type":"quest ion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1594096,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":8805,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1602910,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":4776,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1607693,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under  +<sub>n< /sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":2549,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1610246,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"False","explain":true,"explanation":"multiples of a divisor is a generator.","explanation_history":["multiples of a divos","multiples of a divo","multiples of a divisor is a generoator","multiples of a divisor is a generoato","multiples of a divisor is a generoat","multiples of a divisor is a generoa","multiples of a div isor is  a genero","multiples of a divisor is a generator."],"response_history":["True","False"],"rt":68406,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1678656,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":6478,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1685140,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"S ometimes","response":"Always","explain":true,"explanation":"The two numbers being the same makes it this way.","explanation_history":["Sometimes a ","The two numbers being the same makes it this way."],"response_history":["Sometimes","Always"],"rt":34259,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1719408,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes","Always","Never"],"rt":19384,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1738810,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue  to cont inue.","rt":2505,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1741321,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"26","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["26"],"rt":3087,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1744410,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":7379,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1751792,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Trig 1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Trig 1"],"rt":21716,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1773513,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":11401,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1784922,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"4 - used it but not often or recently","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4 - used it but not often or recently"],"rt":12112,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1797039,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4807,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1801851,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":4082,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1805935,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4987,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1810926,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Male"],"rt":4361,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1815292,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["English"],"rt":6587,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1821882,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":7348,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1829237,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusing, and the third one, i apologize if it seems like I didnt try. Now i wish I did write notes about the math principles.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apoligize for the lac","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apoligize for the la","I was de eply con fused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apoligize for the l","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apoligize for the ","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apoligize for the","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apoligize for th","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apoligize for t","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, an d the th ird one, i apoligize for ","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apoligize for","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apoligize fo","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apoligize f","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apoligize ","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apoligize","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of  confusti ng, and the third one, i apoligiz","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apoligi","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apolig","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apoli","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apologize for","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apologize fo","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of conf usting,  and the third one, i apologize f","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apologize if it seems like I didnt try. I wish now that","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apologize if it seems like I didnt try. Now i wish I did write everything dow","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apologize if it seems like I didnt try. Now i wish I did write every","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apologize if it seems like I didnt try. Now i wish I did write ever","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The fi rst set  of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apologize if it seems like I didnt try. Now i wish I did write eve","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apologize if it seems like I didnt try. Now i wish I did write ev","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apologize if it seems like I didnt try. Now i wish I did write e","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusting, and the third one, i apologize if it seems like I didnt try. Now i wish I did write notes about the math principles.","I was deeply confused about inverses and generators. The first set of questions were really easy. The second was sort of confusing, and th e third  one, i apologize if it seems like I didnt try. Now i wish I did write notes about the math principles."],"rt":156220,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":1985461,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]